cplt20.com 2019-09-14

# Privacy Policy CPL T20

CPL Limited ( **we** ) are committed to respecting your privacy and complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws. 

We have provided this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use and protect your information when you visit www.cplt20.com (our **Site** ). We wish to help you make informed decisions, so please take a few moments to read the sections below and learn how we may use your personal information. 

You should read this notice in conjunction with the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.cplt20.com/terms-conditions) of Use for our Site and our products and services, which may set out additional information about our use of your personal information. 

By visiting our Site you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

1|  **Information we may collect from you**  
We may collect and process the following data about you:  
---|---  
1.1|  **Information you give us**  
You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our Site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our Site, subscribe to our service, make enquiries, make a purchase, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our Site, enter a competition, promotion or survey, and if you report a problem with our Site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal description and photograph, date of birth, gender and lifestyle information.   
1.2|  **Information we collect about you**  
With regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information:  
1.2.1| technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;   
1.2.2| information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.   
1.3|  **Information we receive from other sources**  
We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.  
2|  **Cookies**  
2.1| A cookie is a small text file which is placed onto your computer (or other electronic device) when you access our website. We use cookies on our Site to:  
2.1.1| obtain analytical information about your preferences, online movements and use of the internet;  
2.1.2| carry out research and statistical analysis to help improve our content and to help us better understand our visitor requirements and interests;  
2.1.3| target our marketing and advertising campaigns more effectively;  
2.1.4 | make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable.  
2.2| The information we obtain from our use of cookies will not usually contain your personal data. Although we may obtain information about your computer or other electronic device]such as your IP address, your browser and/or other internet log information, this will not usually identify you personally.  
2.3| In most cases we will need your consent in order to use cookies on this website. The exception is where the cookie is essential in order for us to provide you with a service you have requested (e.g. to enable you to put items in your shopping basket and use our check-out process).  
2.4| If you visit our Site when your browser is set to accept cookies, we will interpret this as an indication that you consent to our use of cookies and other similar technologies as described in this Privacy Policy. If you change your mind in the future about letting us use cookies, you can modify the settings of your browser to reject cookies or disable cookies completely.  
2.5|  **Third-party cookies**  
We work with third-party suppliers who may also set cookies on our website, for example Facebook and Google. These third-party suppliers are responsible for the cookies they set on our site. If you want further information please go to the website for the relevant third party.   
2.6|  **How to turn off cookies**  
If you do not want to accept cookies, you can change your browser settings so that cookies are not accepted. If you do this, please be aware that you may lose some of the functionality of this website. For further information about cookies and how to disable them please go to: www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org  
3|  **Uses made of the information**  
We use information held about you in the following ways:  
3.1|  **Information you give to us**  
We will use this information:  
3.1.1| to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;  
3.1.2| to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;  
3.1.3| to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data;  
3.1.4| to notify you about changes to our service;  
3.1.5 | to ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.   
3.2|  **Information we collect about you**  
We will use this information:  
3.2.1| to administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;  
3.2.2| to improve our Site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;   
3.2.3| to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;  
3.2.4| as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure;  
3.2.5| to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you; and  
3.2.6 | to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Site about goods or services that may interest you or them.  
3.3|  **Information we receive from other sources**  
We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).  
4|  **Disclosure of your information**  
4.1| We may share your personal information with any member of our group of companies.  
4.2| We may share your information with selected third parties including:  
4.2.1| business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you;  
4.2.2| advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others;   
4.2.3| analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Site; and   
4.3| We may disclose your personal information to third parties:  
4.3.1| in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;  
4.3.2| if CPL Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.  
4.4| If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use for our Site and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of CPL Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
5|  **Where we store your personal data**  
5.1| The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  
5.2| Please be aware that communications over the internet, such as emails/webmails, are not completely secure. Your communications may route through a number of countries before being delivered – this is the nature of the World Wide Web/internet. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.  
6|  **Your rights**  
6.1| You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info@cplt20.com.  
6.2| Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.  
7|  **Changes to our privacy policy**  
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.  
8|  **Contact**  
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@cplt20.com.
